// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'In I Dream of Jeanie, where did Tony find Jeanie? ', 
      a: 'A market in Marrakesh', 
      b: 'A beach',
      c: 'The moon',
      d: 'His backyard',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In I Love Lucy, what was Lucy NOT known for?', 
      a: 'Her terrible singing voice', 
      b: 'Joining Ricky’s act',
      c: 'Red hair',
      d: 'Terrible cooking',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'On Bewitched, what would Samantha’s mother NOT call her husband?', 
      a: 'Darwin', 
      b: 'Durwood',
      c: 'Darrin',
      d: 'Dobbin',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The creator of Gilligan’s Island said it was a metaphor for ...', 
      a: 'The American dream', 
      b: 'Hell',
      c: 'Retirement',
      d: 'The seven deadly sins',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who guest starred as “Mork” on a series of episodes in Happy Days?', 
      a: 'Tom Hanks', 
      b: 'Robin Williams',
      c: 'Harvey Keitel',
      d: 'Ron Howard',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the Brady Bunch, which sibling was Jan jealous of?', 
      a: 'Marcia', 
      b: 'Greg',
      c: 'Peter',
      d: 'Cindy',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What 60’s rock band had a TV show also featured on Nick at Nite?', 
      a: 'The Yardbirds', 
      b: 'The Beatles',
      c: 'The Animals',
      d: 'The Monkees',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year did Nick at Nite start?', 
      a: '1979', 
      b: '1985',
      c: '1992',
      d: '1995',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a catchphrase from Get Smart?', 
      a: 'I’m Mister Ed', 
      b: 'Sorry Chief',
      c: 'Car 54 where are you?',
      d: 'Probably my imagination',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was not a character in "The Munsters"', 
      a: 'Herman', 
      b: 'Lily',
      c: 'Grandpa',
      d: 'Fester',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};